question_data=[
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
                ]
            },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
                ]
            },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
                ]
            },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person&#039;s life expectancy.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
                ]
            },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
                ]
            },
    {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
                ]
            },
    {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
                ]
            },
    {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing &quot;Spoons&quot; as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
                ]
            },
    {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
                ]
            },
    {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
                ]
            }

]
